[{"answer": "Nope", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Really, really", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Okay, I'll tell you. Do you know the muffin man", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The muffin man", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes, I know the muffin man, who lives on my friend", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The muffin man", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, she's married to the muffin man", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "The muffin man", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The muffin man", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "She's married to the muffin man", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Three? One? Three", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Okay, okay, uh, number three", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, aye", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Wait a second. Donkeys don't have sleeves", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Come on, Donkey. I'm right here beside ya, okay? For emotional support., we'll just tackle this thing together one little baby step at a time", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Really, really", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Okay, that makes me feel so much better", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Okay, don't look down. Don't look down. Don't look down. Keep on moving. Don't look down.  Shrek! I'm lookin' down! Oh, God, I can't do this! Just let me off, please", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Just, Donkey", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh, I'm sorry. Do what? Oh, this?", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "And, uh, that one, that's Throwback, the only ogre to ever spit over three wheat fields", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "The stars don't tell the future, Donkey. They tell stories. Look, there's Bloodnut, the Flatulent. You can guess what he's famous for", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Never mind, Donkey", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, this is one of those dro", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, this is one of those dro", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Why do you want to talk about it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Why do you want to talk about it", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm not blocking", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What?", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, good morning, Princess", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What he's basically saying is he likes to get..", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "That's bad", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Why? What's wrong", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend's hurt. my friend's hurt? Oh, no, my friend's gonna die", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah. An ogre", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Aah", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No, help", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Perfect! Never been better", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You don't have to tell me anything, Princess. I heard enough last night", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yeah? So what", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I know you talked to her last night. You're great pals, aren't ya? Now, if you two are such good friends, why don't you follow her home", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I told you, didn't I? You're not coming home with me. I live alone! My swamp! Me! Nobody else! Understand? Nobody! Especially useless, pathetic, annoying, talking donkeys", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah. You know what? You thought wrong!", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes, my half. I helped rescue the princess. I did half the work. I get half the booty. Now hand me that big old rock, the one that looks like your head", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "No, you back off", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Our swamp", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You let go", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Love me? She said I was ugly, a hideous creature. I heard the two of you talking", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " She wasn't talking about me? Well, then who was she talking about", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Hey, that's what friends are for, right", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Hey, that's what friends are for, right", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Friends", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I, I love you", "docId": "Shrek.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Really, really", "qsentId": 56}]